<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>I don&#39;t really know what I&#39;m doing lol</title>
    <link>https://www.skang.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on I don&#39;t really know what I&#39;m doing lol</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 20:16:44 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.skang.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LG UltraFine 5k on Linux and Windows</title>
      <link>https://www.skang.dev/blog/lg-5k/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 20:46:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skang.dev/blog/lg-5k/</guid>
      <description>This is yet another post about attempting to get the LG UltraFine 5k working on Linux/Windows.
TLDR: It works at a 4k resolution on my desktop and 5k from my Macbook Pro.
Why are you doing this? The LG UltraFine 5k is a really gorgeous monitor that&amp;rsquo;s (unfortunately) a unique product in the market right now.
There seems to be no other product with the following feature sets:
 A glossy panel 5k resolution Good color reproduction High DPI A single cable docking solution through Thunderbolt Doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a LOUD or GAMER design Camera, speakers, and mic built in  The most attractive of above listed features is the ability to use the Monitor as a docking solution, where I can use a single cable and have all my peripherals be detected alongside it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.skang.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 20:16:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skang.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Just another software engineer blogging about Kubernetes, jazz, or whatever else interests me.
Here have a disclaimer text This is my personal blog. The views expressed on these pages are mine alone and not those of my employer.
I may post incorrect things on here or just opinions. At times, you may not agree with these opinions, or how I choose to express them and that&amp;rsquo;s fine.
I make no promises of being free of bias, nor do I promise to be always factually correct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First blog post</title>
      <link>https://www.skang.dev/blog/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 20:00:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skang.dev/blog/first/</guid>
      <description>This is my blog, I hope to post some useful information for other folks hacking at various things here and work on my writing skills.
&amp;hellip;There&amp;rsquo;s not much here yet, but look forward to some more content!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>